bagtheweb.com 2018-11-05

# privacy_policy - Bag The Web

We've detected that your browser may be outdated. We recommend you upgrade your browser to a more recent version. 

For the best BagTheWeb experience, we recommend using [Google Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome). . 

Your privacy is critically important to us. At BagTheWeb we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our bagging service, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to permanently delete any content.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

BagTheWeb Inc. (“BagTheWeb”) operates several websites including [www.bagtheweb.com](https://www.bagtheweb.com/) and [ambiently.com](http://ambiently.com/). It is BagTheWeb policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, BagTheWeb collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. BagTheWeb’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how BagTheWeb’s visitors use its website. From time to time, BagTheWeb may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

BagTheWeb also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. BagTheWeb does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to BagTheWeb’s websites choose to interact with BagTheWeb in ways that require BagTheWeb to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that BagTheWeb gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [www.bagtheweb.com](https://www.bagtheweb.com/) to provide a username and email address. In each case, BagTheWeb collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with BagTheWeb. BagTheWeb does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

BagTheWeb may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, BagTheWeb may monitor the most popular bags on the BagTheWeb.com site. BagTheWeb may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, BagTheWeb does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

BagTheWeb discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on BagTheWeb’s behalf or to provide services available at BagTheWeb’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using BagTheWeb’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. BagTheWeb will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, BagTheWeb discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when BagTheWeb believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BagTheWeb, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a BagTheWeb website and have supplied your email address, BagTheWeb may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with BagTheWeb and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. BagTheWeb takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. BagTheWeb uses cookies to help BagTheWeb identify and track visitors, their usage of BagTheWeb website, and their website access preferences. BagTheWeb visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using BagTheWeb’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of BagTheWeb’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by BagTheWeb and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BagTheWeb may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in BagTheWeb’s sole discretion. BagTheWeb encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Note: This is a modified document based on an original kindly made available by WordPress.com under a **Creative Commons Sharealike** license.
